{
    "id": "346f547da19547ef86103c07aea31be3",
    "title": "Unless, Providing, Provided, And As Long As Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "We can win the championship, .......................... we avoid bad injuries.",
            "description": "Providing has a similar meaning to if.",
            "answers": [
                "providing",
                "Unless"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "1592750ee3034ba9859af4f73ec39428"
        },
        {
            "question": "I will leave now, .............................. there is anything left to do now.",
            "description": "Unless has a similar meaning to if not. ",
            "answers": [
                "unless",
                "as long as"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "7b7ae7f426c349a0a576465f025d8e26"
        },
        {
            "question": "We can hold the party in the garden ............................. it doesn't rain.",
            "description": "Provided means on condition that.",
            "answers": [
                "provided",
                "unless"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "b6ef620766174629a24adc77d3787d5f"
        },
        {
            "question": "The public will be admitted to the galleries, ........................... they make a donation.",
            "description": "Providing means on condition that.",
            "answers": [
                "unless",
                "providing"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "b58f8574f20642fdbe264d996918d11e"
        },
        {
            "question": "You can keep the puppy ................................... you promise to take care of it.",
            "description": "Both expressions are possible here. ",
            "answers": [
                "as long as",
                "provided that"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "a5de178dcd7e47629d4766538c4f19ce"
        },
        {
            "question": "You can take my car ............................... you drive carefully.",
            "description": "As long as and provided that mean 'on condition that'.",
            "answers": [
                "as long as",
                "provided that",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "d6ef89d588e04c97b6ec7f1b1c9faf00"
        },
        {
            "question": "I can't help you ............................ you tell me what is wrong.",
            "description": "Unless means if not. The above sentence can also be written as: I can help you if you tell me what is wrong. ",
            "answers": [
                "unless",
                "providing"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "d8cc676bcc824132b079053497ee176f"
        },
        {
            "question": "I can help you ............................... you tell me what is wrong.",
            "description": "Provided that means on condition that.",
            "answers": [
                "unless",
                "provided that"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "7e836ae0cbe3468e9e603a98bd2e82d6"
        },
        {
            "question": "He wouldn't eat anything .................................. he cooked it himself.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "providing",
                "unless"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "fbe287c2ec89413da6c09d3833db54f2"
        },
        {
            "question": "You can take this seat, ............................... no one has reserved it.",
            "description": "Providing and as long as are possible here. They both mean 'on condition that'.",
            "answers": [
                "unless",
                "providing",
                "as long as"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "59fac1048b07460fa1cf887de15237ff"
        },
        {
            "question": "My parents don't care who I marry .......................... I am happy.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "as long as",
                "unless"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "6ac60b6eeacf4ebea31054da4b699fc6"
        },
        {
            "question": "You can go out now .............................. you finish your homework first.",
            "description": "All of these expressions mean the same,",
            "answers": [
                "providing",
                "provided that",
                "as long as",
                "All of these"
            ],
            "correct": 3,
            "id": "59f90d95105f47ccad288cd7502f33a2"
        }
    ]
}